Guide to the Records of the New York University Men's and Women's Glee Clubs and Choral Arts Society RG 39.12
New York University Archives
Records of the New York University Men's and Women's Glee Clubs and the University Choral Arts Society
1866-2008
RG 39.12
New York University Archives
5.0 linear feet (15 boxes)
The New York University Men's and Women's Glee Clubs and Choral Arts Society collection is composed of concert programs and ephemera, newspaper clippings, photographs, and audio recordings spanning the clubs' long history.
History of the New York University Men's and Women's Glee Clubs and the University Choral Arts Society
In 1873, the New York University Men's Glee Club, composed of seventeen young men, sang their first formal concert in New York's Chickering Hall. The Club continued to grow in size and popularity under the direction of Dr. Joseph H. Bryan, founder and conductor of the Men's Glee Club through 1892. The NYU Men's Glee Club served as a model for other universities and performed around the world on some of the biggest stages. In 1934, the Club was the first to establish a training camp held one week prior to the university’s opening in September and soon thereafter, the Winter Training Camp was added to the club’s intercession schedule. Inspired by the NYU Men's Glee Club’s dedication, many college choruses created their own training programs. The Club performed 38 concerts at the then NYU-owned Town Hall and has toured in Puerto Rico, Jamaica, and throughout Europe and the United States. The Men's Glee Club was also featured on the Ed Sullivan show and chosen to sing before Pope Paul II at the Vatican, the Rockefeller Center tree lighting ceremony, the Macy’s Thanksgiving Day parade, and in 1956 performed atop the Pepsi Cola sign in Times Square. The Men's Glee Club was just one of the many choral singing groups at the University. In 1965, the Women’s Glee Club was created and four years later, Professor and Conductor E. Jon de Revere consolidated the Men's and Women’s clubs with the School of Education Chorus to form the New York University Choral Arts Society. Professor de Revere also started the Goliards, a twelve-man group selected from the Men’s Glee Club. In 1962, the Goliards were selected by the U.S. Department of State to do a USO Tour in Germany and France, and the elite group also provided annual Christmas entertainment at the Caneel Bay Plantation in the U.S. Virgin Islands from 1964 to 1970.
The Men's Glee Club was revived in 2012.
Scope and contents
Series I largely contains Men's Glee Club concert programs from 1866 to 2008. Many of the programs document the club's annual performance at the then-NYU owned Town Hall. Other ephemera within this series includes concert advertisements and event calendars.
Series II consists of correspondence from and to Glee Club members, conductors, and alumni.
Series III is largely composed of publications about the Men's Glee Club. In addition to newspaper clippings, student publications like the Glee Club Bulletin (1938-1967) and Encore described the club's activities. This series also includes songbooks utilized by club members.
Series IV contains recordings of the Men's Glee Club performances between 1942 and 1970. Most recordings are of the club's annual Town Hall concert.
Series V contains photographs of the Men's and Women's Glee Club ranging from 1898 to the 1980s. The oldest images of the Men' s Glee Club are yearbook portraits. Many Glee Club concerts and tours were photographed including the Times Square performance, Rockefeller Center Tree Lighting Ceremony, and the Goliards at Caneel Bay. In addition, there are many images of the Men's Glee Club training camps. Finally, several disassembled scrapbooks within this series, such as the Heights Women's Chorus scrapbook, contain photographs and other club ephemera.
Series VI holds additional Men's Glee Club recordings.
Series VII contains oversized photographs of the Men's Glee Club.
Source of Acquisition
These materials were transferred to the University Archives from a storage room in the School of Education Building in 1996.
Arrangement
The New York University Men's and Women's Glee Clubs and Choral Arts Society collection is organized into seven series. The material within each series is arranged chronologically. Series IV is further divided into eighteen subseries based on each album's date.
Concert programs and ephemera
Correspondence
Publications
Concert recordings
Photographs
Audiovisual recordings
Oversized material
Access Restrictions
Material pertaining to individual student records may be restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA).
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection.
For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
New York University. Glee Club.; Choral singing; Ensemble singing; Music-halls.; Music.; Phonograph records; Songs
- Series I: Concert programs and ephemera
  - The University Item Program, 1 Mar. 1866 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - NYU Quartette Summer Tour Program and Tickets, 1868 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1886 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Concert of the NYU Glee Club Program, 13 May 1895 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Opening Concert and Dance Program, 6 Jan. 1911 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - NYU Musical Clubs' Opening Concert Program, 1912, 8 Jan. 1912 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - NYU Musical Clubs' Opening Concert Program, 1915, 8 Jan. 1915 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Southern Concert Tour Program and Schedule, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Glee Club Concert Program, 1927, 30 April 1927 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1932, 5 Mar. 1932 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 1934, 15 Dec. 1934 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Town Hall Concert Poster, 14 Dec. 1935 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 13th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 9 Dec. 1939 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 14th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 14 Dec. 1940 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 16th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 19th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 4 Dec. 1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 20th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 10 Dec. 1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 21st Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 6 Apr. 1951 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 13th Annual Spring Concert Program, 10 May 1952 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 17th Annual Camp Concert Program, 17 Sept. 1953 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 24th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 11 Dec. 1953 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Horace Greeley High School Concert Program, 31 Jan. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - School Playground Fund Concert Program, 23 Sept. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 25th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 10 Dec. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 16th Annual Spring Festival Program, 29 Apr. 1955 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 26th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 9 Dec. 1955 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 28th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 13 Dec. 1957 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Glee Club Concert Ad., Nov. 1958 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - St. David's Society Concert Program, 31 Oct. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 29th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 11 Dec. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 30th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 9 Dec. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Outline of Events, July, 1961 - July, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 31st Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 8 Dec. 1961 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs and Outline of Events, 1965 - 1966 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Outline of Events, July 1966 - July 1967 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs and Ad., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 39th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 11 Dec. 1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 40th Annual Town Hall Concert Program, 10 Dec. 1971 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Centennial Year Concert Program, 15 Apr. 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bon Voyage and Annual Winter Concert Program, 18 Dec. 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 110th anniversay Celebration Program, 7 May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Glee Club Concert Programs, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 120th Anniversary Concert Program, 17 Apr. 1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 135th Anniversary of Choral Singing Celebration Program, 8 Nov. 2008 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Undated Glee Club Concert Programs (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Record labels, 1942, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Series II: Correspondence
  - 1927-1928 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1936, 1938, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1962, 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Constitution and executive board, 8 Sept. 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Letter to alumni, 26 Apr. 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Series III: Publications
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1877, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1926, 1927, 1931, 1937, 1953, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Amherst Collge Series, Choral Music Songbook, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Crucification, Sacred Song by Pearl G. Curran, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dover Beach Song Book by Samuel Barber, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mastersongs by Great Composers, Franz Liszt, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mauro Giuliani, Sonate fur Gitarre, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Songs Sacred and Secular by Charles Gounod (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Vocal Composition by C. Whitney Coombs, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - NYU Glee Club Songbooks, 1860, 1900, 1901, 1909, 1915 (Box PUB 1)
  - NYU Glee Club Songbooks, 1926, 1931, 1937, 1938, 1942, 1948, 1980 (Box PUB 2)
  - Glee Club Bulletin (bound), 1938-1967 (Box PUB 3)
  - Glee Club Bulletin (bound), 1953-1967 (Box PUB 4)
  - Glee Club Bulletin and Encore (unbound), 1938, 1943, 1944, 1953, 1957, 1959, 1960, 1961, 1964-1969 (Box PUB 5)
- Series IV: Concert recordings
  - Subseries A: 16th Annual Town Hall Concert, 12 Dec. 1942
    - Album #16: Side #1, "Dec. 12, 1942"; Side #3, "New York University", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Album #16: Side #2, "Dec. 12, 1942," Side #4: "Dec. 12 1942", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Album #16: Side #5, "Dec. 12, 1942"; Side #7, "Dec. 12, 1942", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Album #16: Side #6, "Dec. 12, 1942"; Side #8, "Dec. 12, 1942", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Album #16: Side #9, "Town Hall"; Side #11, "Dec. 12, 1942", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Album #16: Side #10, Untitled; Side #12, "Dec. 12, 1942", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Album #16: Side #13, "Dec. 12, 1942"; Side #15, "Dec. 12, 1942", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Album #16: Side #14, "Dec. 12, 1942"; Side #16, "Town Hall", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Album #16: Side #17, "Dec. 12, 1942"; Side #19, "Town Hall", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Album #16: Side #18, "Dec. 12, 1942"; Side #20, "Dec. 12, 1942", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Album #16: Side #21, "Dec. 12, 1942"; Side #22, "Dec. 12, 1942, Town Hall", 12 Dec. 1942 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: 17th Annual Town Hall Concert, 14 April 1947
    - Album #17: Side #1, "Palisades"; Side #3, "Plorate, Filii Israel", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Album #17: Side #2, "Now Let Every Tongue Adore Him"; Side #4, "Hospodi Pomiloi", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Album #17: Side #5, "Zompa, Llari Llira"; Side #7, "'Mpravisata", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Album #17: Side #6, Untitled; Side #8, "Vale of Tuoni & Forest Invocation", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Album #17: Side #9, "Gute Nacht"; Side #3, "Thank God for a Newborn Day", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Album #17: Side #10, "Hunting Song"; Side #12, "The Inner Light", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Album #17: Side #13, "Alleluia"; Side #15, "Begin the Beguine", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Album #17: Side #14, "Carol of the Bells"; Side #16, "Selections", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Album #17: Side #17, "Encores"; Side #19, "Have You Seen but a Whyte Lillie Grow?", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Album #17: Side #18, "Shepard, Thy Demeanor Vary"; Side #20, "Do Not Go, My Love", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Album #17: Side #21, "Miranda"; Side #23, "When the Foeman Bares His Steel", 19 April 1947 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Subseries C: 19th Annual Town Hall Concert, n.d.
    - Album #19: Side #1, Untitled; Side #3, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Album #19: Side #2, Untitled; Side #5, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Album #19: Side #4, Untitled; Side #6, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Album #19: Side #7, Untitled; Side #9, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Album #19: Side #8, Untitled; Side #10, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Album #19: Side #11, Untitled; Side #13, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Album #19: Side #15, Untitled; Side #17, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Album #19: Side #16, Untitled; Side #18, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: 20th Annual Town Hall Concert, n.d.
    - Album #20: Side #1, Untitled; Side #3, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Album #20: Side #2, Untitled; Side #4, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Album #20: Side #5, Untitled; Side #7, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Album #20: Side #6, Untitled; Side #8, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Album #20: Side #9, Untitled; Side #11, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Album #20: Side #10, Untitled; Side #12, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Album #20: Side #13, Untitled; Side #15, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Album #20: Side #14, Untitled; Side #16, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Album #20: Side #17, Untitled; Side #19, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Album #20: Side #18, Untitled; Side #20, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Album #20: Side #21, Untitled; Side #23, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Album #20: Side #22, Untitled; Side #24, Untitled, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Subseries E: 21st Annual Town Hall Concert, 6 April 1951
    - Album #21: Side #1, "The Palisades"; Side #3, "Tenebrae Factae Sunt", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Album #21: Side #2, "Glorious Apollo"; Side #4, "Cherubic Hymn", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Album #21: Side #5, "To Thee Alone be Glory"; Side #7, "Sonata for Cello and Piano", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Album #21: Side #6, "Sonata for Cello and Piano"; Side #8, "Sonata for Cello and Piano", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Album #21: Side #9, "Sonata for Cello and Piano"; Side #11, "An Den Fruhling", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Album #21: Side #10, "Trinklied"; Side #12, "Italian Folk Song", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Album #21: Side #13, "Devce v Haji"; Side #15, "The Monks' March", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Album #21: Side #14, "Hospodi Pomiloi"; Side #16, "Johnny Stiles", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Album #21: Side #17, "The Turtle Dove"; Side #19, "The Musical Trust", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Album #21: Side #18, "Hush'd Be the Camps Today (cont.)"; Side #20, "21 Elegie", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Album #21: Side #21, "21 Elgie (cont.)"; Side #23, "Requiesbro", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Album #21: Side #22, "Danza Berbera"; Side #24, Untitled, 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Album #21: Side #25, "Four Choruses from 'Patience'" part 1; Side #27, "Down in the Valley", 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Album #21: Side #26, "Four Choruses from 'Patience'" part 2; Side #28, Untitled, 6 April 1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Subseries F: 22nd Annual Town Hall Concert, 7 Dec. 1951
    - Album #22: Side #1, "The Palisades"; Side #3, "Tenebrae Factae Sunt", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Album #22: Side #2, "Fire, Fire, My Heart"; Side #4, "I Laid Me Down to Slumber", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Album #22: Side #5, Untitled; Side #7, "Pastorale Variee", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Album #22: Side #6, "Let Us Break Bread Together"; Side #8, "Pastorale Variee", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Album #22: Side #9, "Rhapsodic Espagnole"; Side #11, "Encores", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Album #22: Side #10, ending of "Rhapsodic Espagnole"; Side #12, "Encores", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Album #22: Side #13, "Duckworth Chant"; Side #15, "I've Got Sixpence", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Album #22: Side #14, "Song of the French Partisan"; Side #16, "Hodie Christus Natus Est", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Album #22: Side #17, "Puer Natus"; Side #19, "Sing We Noel Once More", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Album #22: Side #18, "The Holly and the Ivy"; Side #20, "I Saw Three Ships", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Album #22: Side #21, "Scaramouche"; Side #23, "Scaramouche", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Album #22: Side #22, "Scaramouche"; Side #24, "Encores", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Album #22: Side #25, "Old Man Noah"; Side #27, "Plank Hound & Pirate Song", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Album #22: Side #26, "Old Paint"; Side #28, "Songs by Varsity Quartet", 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Album #22: Side #29, Untitled; Side #30, blank side, 7 Dec. 1951 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Subseries G: 26th Annual Town Hall Concert, n.d.
    - Cover Letter, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Album #26: Side #1 Untitled; Side #3 Untitled, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Album #26: Side #2 Untitled; Side #4 Untitled, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Album #26: Side #5 Untitled; Side #7 Untitled, n.d. (Box 6, File 4)
    - Album #26: Side #6 Untitled; Side #8 Untitled, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Album #26: Side #9 Untitled; Side #11 Untitled, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Album #26: Side #10 Untitled; Side #12 Untitled, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Album #26: Side #13 Untitled; Side #15 Untitled, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Album #26: Side #14 Untitled; Side #16 blank, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Album #26a: Side #1, "Cantate Domino..."; Side #3, "Sing We Now of Christmas...", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Album #26a: Side #1, "Cantate Domino..."; Side #3, "Sing We Now of Christmas...", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Subseries H: 27th Annual Town Hall Concert, 27 Dec. 1956
    - Album #27: Side #1, "Cantate Domino"; Side #3, "Chanukah Song", 14 Dec. 1956 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Album #27: Side #2, "Chanukah Song"; Side #4, "Shalom Haveyreem/Hanukkah Poem/Hallelujah Chorus", 14 Dec. 1956 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Album #27: Side #5, "String Quartet Continuity"; Side #7, "Angel's Shepherd, reading...", 14 Dec. 1956 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Album #27: Side #6, "The Birth, reading..."; Side #8, "Bethlehem, reading..", 14 Dec. 1956 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Album #27: Side #9, "The Wise Men, reading..."; Side #11, "The Palisades", 14 Dec. 1956 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Album #27: Side #10, "Deck the Hall...", 14 Dec. 1954 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Subseries J: NG
    - Album: Side #?, 4-14; Side #?, 3, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Subseries K: WQXR, n.d.
    - Album: Side #?, Dec. 18/51, NYU; Side #?, NYU Glee Club, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Subseries L: Glee Club, n.d.
    - Album: Side #?, 4-14; Side #?, 3, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Subseries I: 28th Annual Town Hall Concert, 30 June 1967
    - Memorandum (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Album #28: Side #1, "O Magnum Mysterium..."; Side #3, "Maiden Fair, O Deign to Tell...", 13 Dec. 1957 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Album #28: Side #2, "We Meet Again Tonight Boys..."; Side #4, "Mood Indigo...", 13 Dec. 1957 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Album #28: Side #5, "A Lucka, Lucka Siroka..."; Side #7, "Old Paint...", 13 Dec. 1957 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Album #28: Side #6, "Serenade in the Snow..."; Side #8, "Shenandoah", 13 Dec. 1957 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Album #28: Side #9, "Cantemos Unidos..."; Side #11, "Prayer from 'Lohengrin'", 13 Dec. 1957 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Album #28: Side #10, "Brothers, Sing On..."; Side #12, "High Barbary...", 15 Dec. 1957 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Subseries M: Delta Upsilon Fraternity--New York University Chapel Choir
    - Album: XP40784, "Hail, Delta Upsilon..."; XP40785, "Down Among the Dead Men...", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Subseries N: New York University Book Store
    - Album: "Palisades"; unknown, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Subseries O: Chanson
    - "Chanson"; N/A, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Subseries P: Song of Affirmation
    - Album: Side #1, "Song of Affirmation"; Side 2, "Song of Affirmation", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Subseries Q: Glee Club & Oneonta
    - Town Hall Recording: Exultate Deo, 6 Dec. 1967 (Box 7, Reel 1)
  - Subseries R: NYU Glee Club Miscellanous Recordings
    - Town Hall Concert, tape 4, 12 Dec. 1969 (Box 7, Reel 2)
    - Town Hall Concert, tape 1, 11 Dec. 1970 (Box 7, Reel 3)
    - Town Hall Concert, tape 2, 11 Dec. 1970 (Box 7, Reel 4)
    - Town Hall Concert, tape 3, 11 Dec. 1970 (Box 7, Reel 5)
- Series V: Photographs
  - 1920s (Box PHOTO 1, Folder 1)
  - 1930s (Box PHOTO 1, Folder 2)
  - 1940s (Box PHOTO 1, Folder 3)
  - 1950s (Box PHOTO 1, Folder 4)
  - Times Square Performance, 18 Dec. 1956 (Box PHOTO 1, Folder 5)
  - 1960s (Box PHOTO 1, Folder 6)
  - 1970s (Box PHOTO 1, Folder 7)
  - 1980s (Box PHOTO 1, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Center Tree Lighting Ceremony, 1983 (Box PHOTO 1, Folder 9)
  - Undated candid shots (Box PHOTO 2, Folder 2)
  - Undated group shots (Box PHOTO 2, Folder 3)
  - Undated performances (Box PHOTO 2, Folder 4)
  - Yearbook portraits, 1898-1949 (Box PHOTO 2, Folder 5)
  - Contact sheets, n.d. (Box PHOTO 2, Folder 6)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 1 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 1)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 2 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 2)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 3 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 3)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 5 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 4)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 6 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 5)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 8 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 6)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 10 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 7)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 11 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 8)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 12 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 9)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 13 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 10)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 14 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 11)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 15 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 12)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 16 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 13)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 17 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 14)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 18 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 15)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 19 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 16)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 20 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 17)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 21 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 18)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 22 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 19)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 23 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 20)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 24 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 21)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 25 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 22)
  - 1962 Summer camp album, page 26 (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 23)
  - Scrapbook, pages 1 & 2, n.d. (Box PHOTO 3, Folder 24)